And here it is.
[ Claps ]
[ Sighs ]
♪♪
Ha!
Ho! Whoa! Ho! Whoa!
Ho! Whoa!
What is this?
It's Tom Bondarly,
king of the dirty songs!
[ Whimpers ]
You and your friends used to get this?
All the time.
My uncle showed him to us.
My uncle was awesome.
He lived with my grandpa his whole life.
So did I.
[ Growls ]
You guys gotta see this.
It's so fucking fun!
We gotta get to the restaurant.
Shut up about the fucking restaurant.
Come on. Come on, guys!
Tom Bondarly!
Now, I just want to say,
I was a little worried people didn't like
this kind of stuff anymore.
I had given up on it completely.
I truly love dirty songs.
Now, I haven't done this in a while.
I hope I remember 'em.
[ Sniffles ]
♪ Oh, old Bart Dogg Fuck ♪
♪ Had a dong on my long ♪
♪ Had a dong on my long head ♪
♪ He ♪
♪ He tried to suck it ♪
♪ On a tuffet ♪
Ah!
What the hell did he do?
Hell.
Fucking hell.
I don't remember the words.
We got the gist on.
You can still tell it's dirty.
I should have prepared,
but I just watch TV.
Let's try another one.
♪ Oh, old Arthur James MacLeish ♪
♪ Walked his sweener dog on a leash ♪
What the fuck is it?
Ah! I'm sorry, guys.
I can't remember the words.
I know it's something about
his cock goes in the dog,
he fucks the dog,
and then the dog's dinner is his cum.
Sorry.
Okay.
Uh, keep going.
This sucks.
I don't know why I thought
these were coming back.
They're not coming back.
They're not funny anymore.
I-I've wasted my life.
Or am I just dead wrong?
And you guys are loving them.
All right!
Now comes the time of the night
when I face the wall
and give you guys a chance to jack off.