- What the hell is this?
- It's a cardboard cutout of you, Robert.
You're the guest of honor.
- And we got Kismet Rotisserie.
- Kismet? I didn't know they did catering.
- They did it special.
I don't know what to say.
- That's a first.
[laughter]
- I guess I do know what to say.
Let's party.
[cheers and applause]
- You can do it, brother.
You're in trouble.
[upbeat music]
- Whoo!
- We're thankful!
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
♪ ♪
- Yeah, we'll make sure we lock down Cleveland
before we move forward on that.
- I know, I know.
I'm just a little worried about
what our first quarter earnings report looks like
if that deal ends up dragging into April or beyond.
Now, the other clients in the region
have been patient with us so far.
They can't wait around forever.
God knows what'll happen
if the whole proposal goes belly up.
- Robert?
- Oh, yeah, sorry.
Truly, don't worry about that.
- All right.
Then I'll shut up about that.
- Yeah, no worries.
- ♪ Feelin' right ♪
- Man, I can't believe that they catered this.
- The guy was so nice.
We told him who you were.
We described you.
He knew right away, and he said, "That guy?
I love that guy."
- Amazing.
I do go there a lot.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[ice clinking]
- ♪ Lights and lights, frosty cake ♪
♪ Line the presents up so great ♪
♪ Sing a song, smile and smile ♪
♪ Today's your day ♪
♪ We're gonna go wild ♪
♪ Wild on, wild on ♪
♪ Tonight we go wild on ♪
♪ Tonight we go crazy ♪