(dramatic music)
- Come with me.
Let's use our imagination, shall we?
- Coming to the Candlelight Theater this spring,
Richard Brekke brings his mastery of silent theater
to the stage as Jellybean.
- No props, an empty stage.
Let me paint you a world.
- Using only gesture and emotion,
he creates 73 stories that will leave you
on the edge of your seat.
- And I never talk.
- Watch and wonder as he transports you
to the furthest reaches of your imagination.
- And if I talk, you get money.
But I never talk.
- Audiences across the country have sold out theaters
to marvel at his wordless stories
and try to get him to talk.
- What are you doing?
What is that?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What is that?
What is that?
- What are you doing?
- What is that?
- It's a ring.
(bell dings)
- Richard Brekke.
(bell dinging)