Richard Brekke has entrenched himself in one of the country's most charming eras.
And with his unique craftsmanship, he brings to life 73 tales both as personal as they
are universal.
The fuck is that?
I wanna know now!
Just hold on!
The fuck is that?
Just wait a minute!
I wanna know right now!
Just look at it!
I wanna know now!
I wanna know right now!
The fucking blank, you fucking scumbag!
Lose yourself in the world of the mind.
And don't just come and try and make me talk.
I don't want to talk.
I love this stuff.
I love old stuff.
Only come here if you like that stuff.
If you asked me when I started this how many frats would come, I would have said none.
But now it's like all frats.
All frats and bachelor parties.
Leave me alone!