♪♪
Hey, Candy?
Oh, hi, Robert.
How you doing? H-Happy birthday.
I'm okay. I've been meaning to talk to you
about what happened last week.
I shouldn't have spoken to you like that.
Oh, no, I didn't -- I didn't even think twice about it.
Oh, even if you haven't thought about it,
I'm sorry I was so quick to say
that you weren't allowed to bring in your rats.
I appreciate that.
And I realize I may have treated you unfairly
when Steven brought in his dog,
and I didn't come down on him nearly as hard
as I came down on you when you brought in four rats.
Dogs are to Steven what rats are to me.
Understood.
'Cause I'm the rat mom.
Yeah, well, it's not for me to decide
which animals are worse than others.
Right, because it's -- it's so easy for me
just to open the desk drawer.
They're in there. I take the food.
I put it on the desk, and then I knock it in.
No one knows what I'm doing.
No one knows I have rats in there.
Sure. Either way, I -- I shouldn't have said that.
Maybe I'm a little bit hard on you
because I see you rising at this place,
and -- and I could see you helping to manage it one day.
[ Chuckles ]
Thank you, Robert. I --
So, that's all.
I just wanted to say sorry and Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas and happy birthday.
Thank you.
Thanks.
♪ Light the lights, frost the cake ♪
♪ Line the presents up so great ♪
♪ Sing the song, smile the smile ♪
♪ Today's your day ♪
♪ We're gonna go wild, wild on, wild on ♪
♪ Tonight we go wild on ♪
♪ Tonight we go crazy ♪
Oh, my God!
I drank fucking dog shit!
Who put dog shit in the cup?!
Who did it?!
♪♪
♪ Yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(upbeat music)