- I'm trying to say-- - Where you think
it comes from, the bank?
(audience laughing)
- Barley, I just-- - Hold on a second.
I gotta do something really fast.
What the fuck?
Is everything all right?
Not sure.
- I'll size you up and I'll cut you down.
- But if I feel like you're getting the best of me,
I have no problem being on my phone the whole show.
- It's impossible to keep gas prices this high.
- That's exactly the point I made two seconds ago.
- Fuck!
- Barley? - Hold on a second.
I gotta do something for my mom.
She's not getting any hot water.
- Well, one thing I-- - Hold on, hold on.
Everything's crazy at her house.
Hold on one second.
- Is she okay?
Barley? - She can't take a shower.