You did the right thing.
(dramatic music)
♪ I've traveled far, I've traveled wide ♪
♪ So many miles, I'm bleary-eyed ♪
♪ Still I get no place with you ♪
(phone beeps)
- Yeah, you got behind the wheel.
That could have been bad.
- Yeah, well, thanks.
- Fuck, they're trying to make it look fake!
God damn it!
- Make what look fake?
- The hat and the cigar.
- You're driving with the driving crooner, baby.
(dramatic music)
♪ Continental travel ♪
- Fuck, fuck, fuck!
They're trying to make it look fake!
- Slow down!
- You gotta be right next to me for it to look real.
You gotta be right next to me.
Everybody tries to make it look fake, fuckers.
I bet you didn't know you were driving
with the driving crooner, did you?
Or working with the driving crooner.
- No, I didn't know you do this.
- Oh yeah, I do this.
I own this.
- You own what?
- Thedrivingcrooner.com, baby.
Don't you love it?
(car engine roaring)
I gotta figure out how to make money on this thing.
It's simply too good.
The dream is to have five cars going around state walk.
- Hey, watch out for this guy here.
- Fuck, he's trying to steal my decals!
- What the hell are you doing?
- Sorry about that.
I thought he was trying to steal my decals.
- He was walking his dog.
- He was walking right up the car.
He was trying to rip the hat off.
He was trying to rip the cigar off.
- How the hell would he do that?
- I don't know.
Some people hate this, James.
I don't know what it is, but they fucking hate it.
There's people that wanna kill me, James.
- They wanna kill you for doing the driving crooner?
- Yeah.
- Jesus.
- Gotta figure out how to make money on this.
I really want to.
Hey, what do you think of Richard from work?
He's got that big Cadillac.
I could just slap the sticker on the side.
He'd be a perfect driving crooner.
That would generate revenue.
- Yeah, man, maybe.
- Yeah!
Yes, James!
Fuck, fucking hell!
Fuck, oh no!
- What?
- Frat boys, they're gonna try and run us off the road.
Roll up the window.
- There's nothing on it.
- Oh, we know what's on it.
- There's no stickers on it.
- Yes, there is.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna fucking kill you, driving crooner!
- Are you all right?
- I'm so sick of this.
Why do they hate it so much?
(sighing)
When I was a kid, I fell into a river
and a fish bumped me out of the water.
I was supposed to die,
but a fish bumped me out with its nose.
That was the earth telling me
I was supposed to do something great.
And I know that's the driving crooner.
It has to be.
You know what I mean, James?
I'm so sick of this!