You really can't do anything when someone says shut up.
I hadn't been on a date in 10 years.
TK Jeweler sold me a watch that exploded every which way.
You said it exploded when you bent your wrist?
Yeah, I was showing my date a picture of Bunny
and showing her what the bunny was doing.
and then 150 springs hit her in the face.
The springs went in her soup.
There was 300 springs in her soup.
Sounds like a really bad date.
Sucked!
Just try not to interrupt.
You said millions of people were gonna hear our voices.
And I'm just a man looking for love.
A lot of these places, they try and rip off people like me,
people who are looking for love.
Well, I guess we could leave some of it in
if it will help some people.
[ Applause ]
Yeah, Rhett, it's a little going on.
- A little goes a long way.
A little goes a long way.
All you gotta do is try.
- All right, from the top, let's go.
(audience cheering)
- All right, and action.
- Somewhere in the static.