All right, guys, we're getting some commentary
from the sound guys.
You're just supposed to laugh, not talk.
Was anybody talking?
Was anyone here ripped off by a place called
TK Jewelers and L&L Limos?
And Avani Suits.
Sir, you can't talk. You understand?
Yep.
Okay.
But what about after the laughs?
There's, like, a space.
No, that's what we're saying.
Got it. Won't happen again. Sorry.
What do you mean the limo driver had an...
area you couldn't go in? Oh yeah well he had a piece of plywood painted black
like it was the wall of the limo like it was the end of the limo but I could hear
people in there and there was a part of it that was over the ice tray and
sometimes we'd see
a hand come underneath the plywood and grab the ice tray to pull it to their side.
And the hand had a Super Bowl ring on it.
And every few minutes, the wall would push up like they were trying to get more space.
And when I asked the driver what was going on, he said, "Shut up."