- Hey, where are you going?
- To relax!
I already had my picture taken with the star of the night.
I liked what I did.
- That's because you don't have business deals on the line.
- I do! A ton!
I have 15 investors for the Pelling Ball.
- What the fuck is the Pelling Ball?
- It's a game.
- It doesn't sound fun.
- Okay, I just had six dinners with Bart Lee,
'cause Pelling Ball's not fun.
- Who the hell is Bart Lee?
- You ever heard of John Richter?
- No.
- You know nothing about games.
- Knowing about games isn't cool!
[dramatic music]
♪
- Stop! Stop doing that!
You stop that right now!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop doing that right now!
You stop that right now!
- Yep.
[upbeat music]
- ♪ This must be my day now ♪