That's kind of cheesy or corny, but it was actually really inspiring.
Oh wow, that's so interesting.
You forget that your co-workers have these full lives.
Oh, that's so true. You forget that when you just see them at work.
Exactly.
Enjoy it. You swear to God.
I swear to fucking God I do.
If this is true, you are my favorite person.
I swear to God.
Those guys are kind of being like really loud.
Oh, they're just having fun.
I like the way you look at the world.
Yeah, I just try to look at it through that perspective.
It's easy to do once you try to do it.
A lot of folks don't care to try.
Very true.
Yeah.
So tell me more about this work retreat.
That sounds so awesome.
Yeah, it was awesome. We were really surprised.
I swear to God.
I was having a beautiful time solo on the kayak.
I see this Mako shark.
It's so fucking close to me.
What?
It's like from me to that guy over there with the plaid shirt and that dog hair.
Which guy?
That guy right there with the plaid shirt and the hair that hangs over his sides like they're dog ears.
The shark was that close?
Dog hair? What the hell are you talking about? Dog hair?
And my boss came and started to do karaoke. We didn't even know she was coming.
Did you know Joey was almost eaten by a shark?
What?
I wasn't almost eaten. It's just the shark was as close to me as that guy whose hair looks like dog ears.
I actually thought that was a dog at that chicken.
Dog?
It's like a Springer Spaniel.
Dog ears?
I grew up with Springers.
Beautiful dogs.
Dog?
I mean, she's cute.