- Now guys keep coming up to me saying,
"What's the next wild thing we're gonna do?"
Is there anything more interesting about you
other than your kids?
- I'll try.
- Please try!
I'm the most popular guy here now!
- He's talking about taking a shower
and then I get an ad for Dove soap.
- No, I'm reading the news and on the side,
all these ads keep popping up for Paw Patrol lunchbox.
- Oh, so you must have kids too.
- Well, I--
- What are we doing next?
What's the next thing?
- What are we gonna do?
I don't want it to be another dance.
- I don't know.
- Let's do something!
- Just relax!
- Oh.
Let's talk about something else.
- What should we talk about?
- Yeah!
- What's the craziest thing you've ever done?
- Oh, wow.
(laughing)
- Okay, okay.
So I'm strapped into this instructor's lap,
who looks like Eddie Van Halen, right?
And I look at him, I say, "I'm a bit nervous."
And he says, "You should be!
We're going way too fast!"
(laughing)
- Guys, leave the dog alone.
We're not doing anything with the dog.